<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Serona</string>
    <string name="face_not_detected">Face shape not detected</string>
    <string name="face_not_detected_body">Please scan your face so we can analyze your facial structure and identify your actual face shape accurately</string>
    <string name="skin_not_detected">Skin Tone not detected</string>
    <string name="skin_not_detected_body">Scan your face to help us identify the skin tone that matches you most accurately</string>
    <string name="guide_title_pre_scan">Why Do You Need to Scan Your Face?</string>

    <string name="face_detected_header">Your Face Shape is \'%s\'</string>
    <string name="skin_detected_header">Your Skin Tone is \'%s\'</string>
    <string name="guide_title_post_scan">Prepare Your Skin Before Applying Makeup!</string>

    <string name="desc_face_oval">Your oval face shape creates a naturally elegant and well-balanced look.</string>
    <string name="desc_face_square">Your square face shape creates a bold and well-defined appearance.</string>
    <string name="desc_face_round">Your round face shape creates a soft and youthful appearance.</string>
    <string name="desc_face_diamond">Your diamond face shape creates a sharp and distinctive appearance.</string>
    <string name="desc_face_rectangle">Your rectangle face shape creates a sleek and structured appearance.</string>
    <string name="desc_face_heart">Your heart face shape creates a graceful and balanced appearance.</string>

    <string name="desc_skin_light">Your fair to light skin tone creates a bright and soft natural glow.</string>
    <string name="desc_skin_medium">Your medium tan skin tone gives a warm, balanced, and healthy appearance.</string>
    <string name="desc_skin_deep">Your deep skin tone creates a rich and striking appearance.</string>

    <string name="guide_pre_1_title">Accurate face shape detection</string>
    <string name="guide_pre_1_body">We analyze your facial structure for more precise and effective makeup recommendations.</string>
    <string name="guide_pre_2_title">Accurate skin tone matching</string>
    <string name="guide_pre_2_body">Your skin tone is analyzed with precision to recommend the shades that suit you best</string>
    <string name="guide_pre_3_title">Personalized makeup recommendations</string>
    <string name="guide_pre_3_body">We use your face-analysis results to select the looks, colors, and makeup tutorials that fit you best</string>

    <string name="guide_post_1_title">Hydrate Your Skin</string>
    <string name="guide_post_1_body">Use a lightweight moisturizer or serum to keep your skin hydrated, helping your makeup apply more smoothly and last longer</string>
    <string name="guide_post_2_title">Apply Primer</string>
    <string name="guide_post_2_body">Primer helps blur pores, smooth skin texture, and make your makeup last longer</string>
    <string name="guide_post_3_title">Protection From Sun Exposure</string>
    <string name="guide_post_3_body">Don’t forget to apply sunscreen to protect your skin from UV exposure and keep your makeup looking flawless</string>
    
    <!--Privacy FAQ-->
    <string name="faq_q1">Does Serona keep my personal data secure?</string>
    <string name="faq_a1">
    Yes, Serona takes the protection of your personal data very seriously.

    Here\'s why:\n
    </string>
    <string-array name="privacy_points">
        <item>We do not share or sell your data to any party for commercial purposes.</item>
        <item>All personal information is encrypted, so only you and our authorized systems can access it.</item>
        <item>We only collect data that is strictly necessary to operate Serona\'s features optimally.</item>
        <item>Privacy and security are Serona\'s core foundations, and all our processes are designed to keep your data safe.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="faq_q2">Does Serona sell my data?</string>
    <string name="faq_a2">
    No. Serona does not and will never sell your data.

    We do not share your personal information with any party for commercial purposes.
    Your data is used solely to operate Serona\’s features and to enhance your experience within the app.
        </string>
    <string name="faq_q3">What data does Serona have about me?</string>
    <string name="faq_a3">
    Serona only has the data you choose to share with us.
    Before we collect any information, you are always asked for your consent first.

    The data you allow us to access is used solely to enhance your experience in the app, for example, to provide color predictions that match your skin tone more personally.

    We do not collect irrelevant data and never use your data beyond the needs of Serona\’s features.
    </string>
    <string name="faq_q4">Is it safe to scan my face on Serona?</string>
    <string name="faq_a4">
    Yes, it is safe.
    Face scanning on Serona is done only with your permission, and your facial images are processed securely.
    We do not store your photos without consent, and facial data is used solely to operate features such as personalized color recommendations based on your skin tone.

    Serona does not share, sell, or use your facial data beyond the needs of the app.
        </string>
    <string name="faq_q5">How can I delete my data?</string>
    <string name="faq_a5">
    You can delete your data at any time through the app by going to Profile > Delete Account.
    When you choose to delete your account, all data associated with you will be permanently removed from Serona\’s system and cannot be recovered.
        </string>
    <string name="faq_q6">Who can access my data?</string>
    <string name="faq_a6">
    Only Serona\’s system and authorized internal team members can access your data—and only to the extent necessary to operate the app’s features.

    We do not grant access to any third parties without your consent, and all access is monitored under strict security standards.
        </string>
</resources>